{"tossups": [{"question": "<em>A recurring character on this show who supported paranoid, right-wing views was Sam Flagg</em>. A female character on this show was once labeled a Communist sympathizer by a Congressional aide and had an affair with conservative Frank Burns. Its theme song was titled \"Suicide is Painless.\" In this show's final episode, B.J. Hunnicutt says goodbye to friend Hawkeye Pierce as they leave Asia. For 10 points, name this TV show about doctors during the Korean War.", "answer": "<em><b><u>M*A*S*H</u></b></em>  {III}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>One past holder of this position wrote</em> The Grand Chessboard <em>and ordered a boost in Radio</em> <em>Free Europe transmission before the signing of SALT II.</em> In the Halloween Massacre, Henry Kissinger was replaced in this position by a man who also held this position under George HW Bush. Another holder of this office was a Polish-American who butted heads with Cyrus Vance. For 10 points, name this post held by Brent Scowcroft, Zbigniew Brzezinski, and currently by Susan Rice.", "answer": "<b><u>National Security Advisor</u></b>  {III}", "metadata": "EM"}, {"question": "<em>In myth, an island now in this country was made by the plow of Gefjon</em> (<b>pr. GEF-yon</b>)<em>.</em> The flag still used by this country allegedly fell from heaven before an 1122 victory for its king. The \"deeds\" of its kings were compiled by Saxo Grammaticus, the ultimate source for a play set here in which a king who had fought \"sledded Polacks on the ice\" reappears to claim that he was poisoned in the ear. For 10 points, what country is conquered by Fortinbras at the end of Shakespeare's <em>Hamlet</em>?", "answer": "Kingdom of <b><u>Denmark</u></b> [or <b><u>Danmark</u></b>]  {III}", "metadata": "MJ"}, {"question": "<em>A pope with this name who ruled for fifteen days succeeded Formosus, whose corpse was put</em> <em>on trial in the Cadaver Synod.</em> Another pope with this name issued the bull <em>Ausculta fili</em> after the arrest of Bernard Saisset. A pope with this name imprisoned his predecessor Celestine V, then proceeded to feud with Philip the Fair. For 10 points, give this shared pope name, the eighth holder of which declared papal supremacy in the bull <em>Unam Sanctam</em>.", "answer": "<b><u>Boniface</u></b>  {III}", "metadata": "JL"}, {"question": "<em>Many of these people were aided by and fought for Bernardo de Galvez.</em> An action against these people included confining them in Annapolis Royal and Grand Pr\u00e9. That campaign against these people was led by Edward Cornwallis and Charles Lawrence. After being deported during <em>Le Grand D\u00e9rangement</em>, or the Expulsion of 1755, many of these people resettled in Louisiana and became known as \u201cCajuns.\u201d For 10 points, name these descendants of French-Canadian settlers.", "answer": "<b><u>Acadian</u></b>s [or <b><u>Cadien</u></b>s; accept <b><u>Cajun</u></b>s before mentioned]  {III}", "metadata": "SH"}, {"question": "<em>Insurgents from this place were trained under the CIA's Ess Tee CIRCUS program at Camp</em> <em>Hale</em>. This place celebrates Uprising Day and Serfs Emancipation Day about 18 days apart, which marks the beginning and end of an invasion. After this place lost the Battle of Chamdo, it was forced to sign the Seventeen Point Agreement. A government-in-exile from this place was established in Dharamsala by Tenzin Gyatso. For 10 point, name this region of China once home to the Dalai Lama.", "answer": "<b><u>Tibet</u></b>  {III}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em>This composer\u2019s two Spanish overtures include a</em> \u201cCapriccio brilliante on the Jota Aragonesa.\u201d The overture to this composer\u2019s second opera used a whole-tone scale to represent the dwarf Finn. His first opera centers on the folk hero Ivan Susanin, whose sacrifice for Michael I helped end the Time of Troubles. For 10 points, what father of Russian classical music wrote the operas <em>Ruslan and Lyudmilla</em> and <em>A Life For the Tsar?</em>", "answer": "Mikhail <b><u>Glinka</u></b>  {III}", "metadata": "CW"}, {"question": "<em>In one war, this leader\u2019s forces killed Ottoman Grand Vizier Daman Ali Pasha at</em> <em>Peterwardein, which led to the treaty of Passarowitz two years later</em>. This man\u2019s victory at Zenta forced the Ottomans to hand over Transylvania and Hungary in the Treaty of Carlowitz. He stopped Louis the Fourteenth\u2019s invasion of his home region before co-commanding an army at Blenheim (<b>pr. BLEN-um</b>). For 10 points, name this Austrian general who won many victories with the Duke of Marlborough in the War of the Spanish Succession.", "answer": "Prince <b><u>Eugene of Savoy</u></b>  {III}", "metadata": "VP"}, {"question": "<em>This man became a celebrity after writing a letter to the Long Beach Press-Telegram in</em> <em>September 1933</em>. This person joined with Robert Earl Clements to use real estate skills to promote their plan, which was called unrealistic by economists. This Union Party co-founder believed Franklin Roosevelt's \"Old Age Assistance\" plan was insufficient. For 10 points, name this physician who proposed what would become Social Security throughout the 1930's.", "answer": "Dr. Francis <b><u>Townsend</u></b>  {III}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>In 2011, this group banned samosas for their resemblance to the Holy Trinity.</em> This group targeted crowds watching the 2010 World Cup in Kampala. Operation Indian Ocean is an ongoing attempt to combat this group. This group claimed responsibility for the 2013 Westgate mall shooting in Nairobi. Many of their attacks target supporters of the AMISOM peacekeeping mission in Mogadishu. For 10 points, name this Somali terrorist group loyal to al-Qaeda.", "answer": "al-<b><u>Shabaab</u></b> [prompt on <b><u>al-Qaeda</u></b> until it is read; do not accept \"Somali pirates\"]  {III}", "metadata": "KG"}, {"question": "<em>The Gould Amendment to this act required a certain form of labelling, while its McNary-Mapes amendments outlined inspection procedures.</em> This law was revised following the deaths of more than a hundred people from elixir sulfanilamide. The Supreme Court declared that the terms of this law could not force Coca-Cola to remove caffeine from their products. Like the Federal Meat Inspection Act, this law was passed in response to Upton Sinclair's <em>The Jungle</em>. For 10 points, name this piece of legislation that paved the way for the establishment of the FDA.", "answer": "<b><u>Pure Food and Drug Act</u></b> of 1906  {III}", "metadata": "KG"}, {"question": "<em>This man attempted suicide by jumping over a staircase railing at Mytchett Place</em>. This person was handcuffed to a guard when leaving a cell, a precaution begun after Robert Ley hung himself. This man apparently killed himself in 1987 while serving as the sole occupant of Spandau Prison. In 1941, he flew to Scotland to try to arrange peace talks between Britain and Germany. For 10 points, name this man who was Nazi Germany's Deputy Fuhrer from 1933 to 1941.", "answer": "Rudolf <b><u>Hess</u></b>  {III}", "metadata": "MC"}, {"question": "<em>In the 1900 gubernatorial election of this state, the loser William Goebel was shot and killed</em> <em>after disputing the election results.</em> Andrew Jackson vetoed a bill appropriating funds for a road in this state to Maysville. Although Confederate General Braxton Bragg won the 1862 battle of Perryville in this state, they fell back for the rest of the war. For 10 points, name this state whose McCoy family feuded with the West Virginian Hatfield family just across the border.", "answer": "<b><u>Kentucky</u> </b>", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This event occurred due to a raid on Oroscopa and was opposed by Corculum.</em> Some victims of this event tried to defend themselves in the Byrsa. The historian Polybius, a friend of its perpetrator, was present at this event, which involved blockading a two hundred ship port. It occurred 3 years after the death of Cato the Elder, who often spoke in favor of it, and it did not actually involve sowing salt. For 10 points, name this event, which ended the 3rd Punic War.", "answer": "<b><u>Sack</u> of <u>Carthage</u></b> [accept answers containing synonyms of sack, like destruction, capture, battle, etc.]", "metadata": "History - Ancient History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>Thomas Duncombe presented a petition written by members of this movement to Parliament,</em> <em>where it was rejected, leading to the Plug Riots.</em> The <em>Northern Star</em> was a newspaper that espoused this movement's ideals, and was founded by Feargus O'Connor. Among the six points pushed for by this movement included equal constituencies and universal male suffrage. For 10 points, name this reform movement in 19th-century Britain named after a \"People's\" document.", "answer": "<b><u>Chartist</u></b>s [or <b><u>Chartism</u></b>]", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This man earned the nickname \"Private 606\" when he injected Paul Ehrlich\u2019s new drug</em> <em>salvarsan into many syphilis patients.</em> This scientist\u2019s most famous discovery was actually first isolated by Howard Florey and Ernst Chain (<b>pr. KINE</b>). He discovered lysozyme when a drop of mucus fell into one of his samples. Contamination of a sample of <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em> with mold led to his serendipitous discovery of the first antibiotic. For 10 points, name this British biologist who discovered penicillin.", "answer": "Sir Alexander <b><u>Fleming</u> </b>", "metadata": "Science - Biology"}, {}, {"question": "<em>Members of this religion participate in \"reasonings.\"</em> An early member of this religion named Leonard Percival Howell was imprisoned by the British. Adherents of this religion follow a mostly vegetarian dietary code called I-tal, read the Holy Piby and Kebra Nagast, and refer to their one god as Jah. Marcus Garvey is an important figure in this religion, as he prophesied the crowning of Haile Selassie. For 10 points, name this Afrocentric religion that places spiritual importance upon dreadlocks.", "answer": "<b><u>Rastafari</u></b>anism", "metadata": "Religion - Religion"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This man designed a marble gallery to be twice as long as the Hall of Mirrors in Versailles</em>. This developer of the idea of \u201cruin value\u201d subverted his master\u2019s scorched earth Nero Doctrine. This man\u2019s largest commission included 130 searchlights and was captured on film in Leni Riefenstahl's <em>Triumph Of The Will.</em> For 10 points, name this creator of the New Reich Chancellery and the Zeppelinfeld, chief architect for the Nazi regime.", "answer": "Albert <b><u>Speer</u> </b>", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>A reporter for this newspaper, Janet Cooke, returned her Pulitzer after fabricating a story</em> <em>about a child drug addict</em>. The publisher of this paper, Katharine Graham, was threatened by Attorney General John Mitchell along with its editor Ben Bradlee. Bob Woodward and Carl Bernstein, while working for this paper, used the information of Deep Throat to expose the Watergate scandal. For 10 points, name this oldest newspaper published in the American capital.", "answer": "<em>The</em> <em><b><u>Washington Post</u></b></em> [prompt on <em><b><u>Washington</u></b></em>; prompt on <em><b><u>Post</u></b></em>]", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>A ruler of this region held the Feast of the Pheasant.</em> Tanquy du Chatel assassinated a ruler of this region known as \"the Fearless.\" The last ruler of this region's duchy became the head of the League of the Public Weal. A ruler of this region led forces that captured Joan of Arc. A duchy that ruled this region lost the Battle of Nancy to Louis XI, who then incorporated it into France.  That duchy's last ruler was Charles the Bold. For 10 points, name this region of eastern France.", "answer": "<b><u>Burgundy</u></b> [or Duchy of <b><u>Burgundy</u></b>]", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>At this location, \"Big Pete\" Aubrey led a non-North Carolina group known as the</em> <em>\"Regulators.\"</em> Dorence Atwater recorded the names of those who died at this place and had it published in Horace Greeley's paper. \"Raiders\" at this place attacked their fellows in order to obtain food until an internal trial stopped them. Its commander, Henry Wirz, was executed after the Civil War. For 10 points, name this notorious Confederate prisoner of war camp where 13,000 men died.", "answer": "<b><u>Andersonville</u></b> Prison [or <b><u>Camp Sumter</u></b>, do not accept \"Fort Sumter\"]", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This leader's efforts resulted in the passage of three Conciliation Bills and the</em> <em>Representation of the People Act.</em> After this person's arrest, Mary Richardson vandalized the <em>Rokeby Venus</em> with a meat cleaver. This activist's hunger strike at Holloway Prison prompted the passage of the Cat and Mouse Act, which outlawed the force-feeding of prisoners. For 10 points, name this activist who founded the WSPU during her fight for women's suffrage in the United Kingdom.", "answer": "Emmeline <b><u>Pankhurst</u></b> [or Emmeline <b><u>Goulden</u></b>]", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This man called for the Convention of Aguascalientes, but did not participate himself</em>. The Zimmermann Telegram was sent to this man\u2019s government. Due to his control over the ports of Tampico and Veracruz, this man was able to collect more revenue than Pancho Villa. This man oversaw the 1917 Constitution, which remains Mexico\u2019s Constitution today. For 10 points, which man overthrew Victoriano Huerta to serve as President during the Mexican Revolution?", "answer": "Jos\u00e9 Venustiano <b><u>Carranza</u></b> Garza", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {}, {"question": "<em>This author wrote a long 1871 essay in response to Thomas Carlyle's \"Shooting Niagara:</em> <em>And After?\"</em> This person argued that great \"native authors\" were needed to raise up \"superb men and women\" to vote in American elections in <em>Democratic Vistas</em>. This poet recalled \"the experience sweet and sad\" of aiding injured soldiers in \"The Wound-Dresser.\" For 10 points, name this poet whose time as a Civil War nurse inspired <em>Drum-Taps</em> and later additions to <em>Leaves of Grass.</em>", "answer": "Walter <b><u>Whitman</u> </b>", "metadata": "Literature - American Literature - Misc Literature"}, {}, {"question": "<em><b><u>An account of this battle recalls how several men drank from a stream mixed with their own</u></b></em> <em><b><u>blood.</u> </b></em><b><u>A commander at this battle created a funeral pyre out of saddles to immolate himself</u></b> <b><u>instead of being killed by the enemy. The losers of this battle were later crushed by the</u></b> <b><u>Gepids at the Battle of (+)</u> Nedao. Thorismund led a decisive charge during this battle after he had earlier wandered into the enemy camp. This battle was won by a coalition led by Flavius (*)</b> Aetius and the Visigoth Theodoric I. For 10 points, name this 451 battle that ultimately halted the Huns' Attila\u2019s invasion of Roman Gaul.", "answer": "Battle of <b><u>Chalons</u></b> [or Battle of <b><u>Catalaunian Plain</u></b>s; or Battle of <b><u>Catalaunian Field</u></b>s]  {III}", "metadata": "CKM"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>The founder of this group was born in Girgir villiage and gave a BBC interview insisting</u></b></em> <em><b><u>the world was flat</u></b></em><b><u>. The leader of this group owns a twitter account whose name means</u></b> <b><u>\u201chouse of monotheism\u201d. Actions taken by this group in Baga forced people to flee into (+)</u></b> <b>Lake Chad and become trapped on the islands there. Recently, this group, which is led by Abubakr Shekau and whose name translates roughly as (*)</b> \u201cwestern education is forbidden\u201d pledged allegiance to ISIL. For 10 points, name this terrorist group that kidnapped hundreds of Nigerian schoolgirls in April 2014.", "answer": "<b><u>Boko Haram</u> </b> {III}", "metadata": "AK"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>This woman symbolized spiritual well being with the concept of \u201cviriditas.\u201d</u></b></em><b><u> Margarethe</u></b> <b><u>von Trotta\u2019s film</u> </b><em><b><u>Vision</u></b></em><b><u> explores the life of this woman, who worked with the approval of</u></b> <b><u>Pope Eugenius III. Jutta von Sponheim taught this woman, who invented a language called</u></b> <em><b><u>lingua (+)</u></b><b> ignota</b></em><b> and recorded her visions in the illustrated book </b><em><b>Scivias</b></em><b>. She depicted a battle between the Devil and Virtue in what is considered the first (*)</b> morality play, <em>Ordo</em> <em>Virtutum</em>. For 10 points, name this medieval German mystic known for her visions and music, an abbess from Bingen.", "answer": "<b><u>Hildegard</u></b> von Bingen [or <b><u>Hildegard</u></b> of Bingen; or <b><u>Saint Hildegard</u></b>]  {III}", "metadata": "CKM"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>This group's supporters wore bunches of rosemary and sea-green ribbons on their hats.</u> </b></em><b><u>This group was opposed by the Grandees, and it inspired the Corkbush Field and Banbury</u></b> <b><u>mutinies. This group's \"Agreement of the People\" manifesto was inspired by John (+)</u></b> <b>Lilburne's ideas and was discussed at the Putney debates. A more radical group, the (*) </b>Diggers, called themselves the \"true\" version of this group. For 10 points, name this political faction which advocated for \"freeborn rights\" and democracy during the English Civil War.", "answer": "<b><u>Leveller</u></b>s  {III}", "metadata": "JB"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>Elizabeth Burgin brought food to people living in these places.</u></b></em><b><u> A monument dedicated to</u></b> <b><u>people who died in these places is located in Brooklyn's Fort Greene Park. The people in</u></b> <b><u>charge of these places were called \"traitors, lost to every sense of shame\" by poet Philip (+)</u></b> <b>Freneau, who himself spent time on one. More people died in these places than in battle during the American Revolution, mostly due to (*) </b>hot and cramped conditions. For 10 points, identify these vehicles exemplified by the HMS <em>Jersey</em>, which were repurposed to house convicts and captured soldiers.", "answer": "<b><u>prison ship</u></b>s [prompt on partial answer]  {III}", "metadata": "KG"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>The first person to collect these objects was Richard TeLinde, although he didn\u2019t realize</u></b></em> <em><b><u>their importance.</u></b></em><b><u> These objects, the first discovered to exceed the Hayflick limit, are the</u></b> <b><u>subject of a book by Rebecca Skloot. At Johns Hopkins, George Gey discovered that they</u></b> <b><u>could remain</u> </b><em><b><u>in vitro</u></b></em><b><u> (+)</u> indefinitely. These objects were taken from a cervical tumor in 1951 and discovered to (*) </b>continue replicating without undergoing apoptosis. For 10 points, name these immortal cells used for research purposes, named from their originator Henrietta Lacks.", "answer": "<b><u>HeLa</u></b> cells [accept <b><u>cell</u></b>s from Henrietta <b><u>Lacks</u></b> until \"Henrietta\" is read]  {III}", "metadata": "VP"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>This franchise\u2019s high water mark in the Stanley Cup playoffs was the 1985 and 1987</u></b></em> <em><b><u>Smythe Division Finals when they were swept by the Oilers both times</u></b></em><b><u>. This franchise used a</u></b> <b><u>million dollar contract to lure Bobby Hull from the NHL when it was established in the</u></b> <b><u>WHA in 1972. Despite a grassroots (+</u>) fundraising drive that kept this franchise in its current home for one more year, it moved and became the (*) </b>Arizona Coyotes in 1996. This franchise\u2019s jersey features a CF-18 Hornet fighter plane. For 10 points, name this NHL team based in the capital of Manitoba.", "answer": "<b><u>Winnipeg</u></b> Jets [or <b><u>Jets</u></b>; prompt on <b><u>Arizona</u></b>, <b><u>Phoenix</u></b>, or <b><u>Coyotes</u></b> before mention because they technically hold the old Jets records]  {III}", "metadata": "MW/PL"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>In an attempt to forestall his execution, his lawyer declared that he was a Prussian, and</u></b></em> <em><b><u>could not be tried by French courts, but this man declared \u201cI am French and I will remain</u></b></em> <em><b><u>French.\u201d</u> </b></em><b><u>This man\u2019s commander hailed him as \u201cthe bravest of the brave\u201d during the</u></b> <b><u>retreat from Russia. This man attacked Wellington\u2019s army at the crossroads of (+)</u> Quatre-Bras two days before leading a coordinated attack on the farmhouse of La Haye Sainte in an 1814 battle in present-day (*)</b> Belgium. For 10 points, name this \u201cmarshal,\u201d the chief subordinate of Napoleon at the Battle of Waterloo.", "answer": "Michel <b><u>Ney</u></b> [or Marshal <b><u>Ney</u></b>; or <b><u>1st Duc d'Elchingen</u></b>; or <b><u>1st Prince de la</u></b> <b><u>Moskowa</u></b>; or Le <b><u>Rougeaud</u></b>; or The <b><u>Ruddy</u></b>; or Le <b><u>Brave des Braves</u></b> until mentioned; or the <b><u>Bravest of the Brave</u></b> until mentioned]  {III}", "metadata": "AG"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>NBC's coverage of this event directly led to the creation of the Huntley-Brinkley Report.</u> </b></em><b><u>This event's keynote speech accused the sitting President of \"peer[ing] down the green</u></b> <b><u>fairways of indifference\" and was given by Tennessee governor Frank (+)</u> Clement. At this convention, a mad scramble for the Vice-Presidential nomination ended on the third ballot when Estes (*) </b>Kefauver defeated John F. Kennedy. For 10 points, name this convention at which Adlai Stevenson was nominated for President for a second time.", "answer": "<b><u>1956</u><u>Democratic</u></b> National <b><u>Convention</u></b> [or <b><u>1956</u><u>DNC</u></b>; prompt on <b><u>Democratic</u> </b>National <b><u>Convention</u></b>]  {III}", "metadata": "DW"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>This leader won a great victory after taking his troops to the town of Yehem and marching</u></b></em> <em><b><u>them through the Aruna mountain pass.</u> </b></em><b><u>This son of Iset extended his dynasty's empire to its</u></b> <b><u>largest extent before dying and passing it on to Amenhotep II. Before a seminal victory</u></b> <b><u>over the Mitanni and the king of (+)</u> Kadesh, this 15th-century BC pharaoh, whose name implies that he was drawn up by an (*)</b> ibis-headed god, took care to deface all monuments of his female predecessor Hatshepsut. For 10 points, name this victor at Megiddo, the third pharaoh of his name.", "answer": "<b><u>Thutmose III</u></b> [or <b><u>Thutmosis III</u></b>][His name means \"drawn up by Thoth\".]  {III}", "metadata": "MJ"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>An artist from this country created a throne and \"tree of life\" made out of guns.</u></b></em><b><u> This</u></b> <b><u>country's capital, nicknamed the \"City of Acacias,\" was once named after explorer</u></b> <b><u>Lourenco Marques. It's not Rwanda, but this country is a member of the Commonwealth</u></b> <b><u>despite not being a (+)</u> British colony. This country's politics have been dominated by the opposing RENAMO and (*) </b>FRELIMO groups. This country's flag notably features an AK-47. For 10 points, name this former Portuguese colony whose namesake channel separates Madagascar from Africa.", "answer": "Republic of <b><u>Mozambique</u></b> [or Rep\u00fablica de <b><u>Mo\u00e7ambique</u></b>]  {III}", "metadata": "KG"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>Charles Phelps succeeded one of this bill's co-sponsors as the Representative from</u></b></em> <em><b><u>Maryland's third district.</u></b></em><b><u> The co-sponsors of this bill wrote an open letter addressed \"To the</u></b> <b><u>Supporters of the Government\" claiming that \"the authority of Congress is paramount\"</u></b> <b><u>and protesting the appointment of Michael Hahn as Governor of (+)</u> Louisiana. This bill required half of a state's voters to take an (*) </b>\"ironclad oath\" in order to readmit a Confederate state to the union. For 10 points, Abraham Lincoln pocket-vetoed what Radical Republican plan for Reconstruction?", "answer": "<b><u>Wade-Davis</u></b> Bill  {III}", "metadata": "DW"}, {"question": "<em><b><u>The Marquis de Custine wrote a travelogue mocking this ruler, who unpopularly forbade</u></b></em> <em><b><u>Eastern Rite Catholics from using the Latin Rite.</u></b></em><b><u> This ruler tightened control of universities</u></b> <b><u>in line with the \u201cOrthodoxy, Autocracy, and Nationality\u201d doctrine laid out by his education</u></b> <b><u>minister Sergei (+)</u> Uvarov. Infantry cadets attempted to overthrow the rule of this tsar in the November Uprising in Poland. The (*) </b>Decembrist revolt broke out in protest of the ascension of this tsar, who died midway through the Crimean War. For 10 points, name this tsar who followed Alexander I.", "answer": "<b><u>Nicholas I</u></b> [prompt on <b><u>Nicholas</u></b>]  {II}", "metadata": "AG"}], "bonuses": []}